I didn't think I could love without language
She spoke some of mine,
Me a little of hers
But there were - gaps
In ____
We start ____ simply
____ smiles,
The same ____
The best ____ are often simplest.
And we are ____,
We make sense.
We ____ to live in each other’s ____ languages
Fixing ____ second-hand sentences
With laughs and ____,
Building homes
In phrases only ____ of us understands.
The day when I ____ how I felt
She sits ____ from me
Humming to ____.
I tell ____ I love her in ____language
And she ____ in mine
And we are ____ together
Even when ____ lose words
Like water ____ in hands
Hands ____ holding
____ squeezing morse code messages
____ brushing ____ fallen eyelashes
____ trees ____ ready ____ winter
We ____ them flow, ____ fall away
Because we don’t ____ every word
For us to find meaning.
Now the gaps between us are thousands of miles long
We still try to cross them
With paper plane letters
And words we think about way too much.
You tell me it's easier
Living in the gaps we left behind
Than to rebuild.
While I live back in a different life
A different language
Feeling your absence stronger than your presence
And wondering
What does this mean for us?