I didn't think I could love without
language.
She spoke some of my me and hers, but
there
were
gaps
in. We start
simply smiles the
same. The best are often simplest. And
we
are we make sense.
We to live in each other's languages,
fixing our secondhand sentences with
laughs
and building
homes in phrases
only of us understand.
The day when I how I felt. She sits from
me hugging
to I tell I love her
in language
and
she in mine
and we are together even when lose words
like water in hands. Hands holding,
squeezing Morse code messages, brushing
fallen eyelashes. Trees ready winter
weave them flow, fall
away because we don't every
word for us to find meaning.
[Music]
Now the gaps between
us are thousands of miles
long. We still try to cross
them with paper plain letters and words
we think about way too much.
You tell me it's
easier living in the gaps we left
behind than to
rebuild. While I live back in a
different
life, a different
language, feeling your absence stronger
than your presence.
I
wonder what does this mean for us?